Meet mickeyhub
Open the enclosure
Graphite upper cover; Graphite bottom shell; Four enclosure screws
Light and listening
Transparent light ring; ReSpeaker XVF3800
Sound and touch
Dual touch displays; XFDZ-3727 speaker
Vision and depth
Arducam B0310; VL53L8CX ToF carrier
Three radar views
Left Rd-03E radar; Right Rd-03E radar; Rear Rd-03E radar
Motion and heading
Grove LSM6DS3 IMU; QMC5883L compass
The main computer
Radxa ZERO 3W
Two controllers
XIAO ESP32S3 Plus; XIAO RP2350
Status and expansion
SSD1306 status OLED; Servo Driver HAT (B)
Serial routing
UART multiplexer A; UART multiplexer B
Power switching
M1 host-power relay; M2 radar-power relay; M16 main-hold relay; M17 retained relay; M15 relay interface
Signal interfaces
M20 serial interface; M21 display interface; M22 retained interface; M42 fan interface
Stored and external power
UPS Module 3S + battery; DC-022B input socket; Rear power-button assembly
Active cooling
5010 four-wire blower
Power and data
Power and data harnesses; Custom carrier PCB
Two internal supports
M01 front support; M04 rear support
Sensor retainers
Display retaining strip; Left radar retainer; Right radar retainer; Rear radar retainer
Locks and fasteners
Light-ring locking key; Power-switch keeper; DC socket keeper; Internal screws and spacers
One integrated mickeyhub